# Juan Daniel Sánchez

Full Stack Web Developer

### CONTACTS



3016869202



juandaniel.25@outlook.com



Linkedin



Github



<u>Portfolio</u>

#### **SKILLS**

- React JS
- Redux
- Node JS Express JS
- PostgreSQL
- Sequelize
- Sass

### **LENGUAGES**

English B2

## **PROFILE**

Full Stack web developer with the ability to learn, work and adapt quickly to constantly changing environments. Responsible, proactive and fully focused on achieving goals. I have more than 1000 hours of experience learning and practice in technologies such as Javascript, React JS, Redux, Node JS, Express JS, PostgreSQL, Sequelize and Sass, as well as teamwork, agile methodologies (SCRUM) and continuous deployment to GitHub.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Full-Stack Teaching Assistant | HENRY

4 months

Bootcamp Pre Course Assistant (Henry Hero) for Full-Stack Development Students

- Guide students in the first steps of the course.
- Assist to solve exercises vía Slack.
- Live lectures to students
- Propose ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes

2020 - 2021 Personal Projects

2015 - 2020 Surgical Technician | IPS Universitaria

### **EDUCATION**

#### **HENRY**

Full Stack Web Developer 2022

**Platzi** 

**React Developer** 2021

**Universidad de Antioquia** Surgical Technician

2011 - 2015